<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Christopher Alonso</title>
    <link>https://christopherja.rocks/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Christopher Alonso</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://christopherja.rocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>OSWE Exam Tips</title>
      <link>https://christopherja.rocks/posts/2020/12/oswe-exam-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 08:53:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://christopherja.rocks/posts/2020/12/oswe-exam-tips/</guid>
      <description>On the heels of passing my OSWE exam i wanted to write up a quick post to reassure people on the difficulty level of the exam. As there seems to be some misinformation regarding exactly how difficult it is. In short i would say its difficult but doable. Alot of posts seem to point in the direction of it being a huge codebase that is impossible to go through. That was not my experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AzureADSync BackDoor</title>
      <link>https://christopherja.rocks/posts/2020/05/azureadsync-backdoor/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 08:53:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://christopherja.rocks/posts/2020/05/azureadsync-backdoor/</guid>
      <description>Recently created a golang binary that dumps credentials from the AD Sync Server and creates a user in azure and assigns it to any group in AzureAD you like. Check out the work done by Adam Chester and Dirk-jan at the following links below as this could have not been possible without their hard work and research. Seriously read those both as everything ive done piggybacks of them.
 Dirk-jan&amp;rsquo;s blog post Adam Chester&amp;rsquo;s blog post  tldr Dump AD Sync creds via powershell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OSCE Exam Tips</title>
      <link>https://christopherja.rocks/posts/2020/04/osce-exam-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 08:53:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://christopherja.rocks/posts/2020/04/osce-exam-tips/</guid>
      <description>Just finished my OSCE Exam. And i wanted to contribute a quick blog post regarding the exam/course since i used alot of these myself to prepare. Ill start by laying out some key things i think that helped me pass and eleborate on each with some more details. Keep in mind this is meant to be very to the point and will not detail my exam experience such as time i took etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phishing AMSI Bypass</title>
      <link>https://christopherja.rocks/posts/2020/02/phishing-amsi-bypass/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 13:07:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://christopherja.rocks/posts/2020/02/phishing-amsi-bypass/</guid>
      <description>How to bypass AMSI (The Simplest Way) I was looking to run my own phishing campaigns on my current organization and was testing office document payloads. I tried the old fashioned VBA in the macro running the shell function as well as some others, and defender caught most if not all of them. Using this tool Macro-Pack works sometimes but often, it would get flagged or the powershell command would not properly run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Splunk-G-Suite-Python-App</title>
      <link>https://christopherja.rocks/posts/2020/02/splunk-g-suite-python-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 13:05:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://christopherja.rocks/posts/2020/02/splunk-g-suite-python-app/</guid>
      <description>Ingesting G Suite Alert Center Logs Into Splunk I was recently tasked with ingesting alot of data from various cloud platforms like AWS &amp;amp; GCP into splunk. Splunk provides very good documentation and provides add-ons for both of these platforms. However for G-Suite (which is like 0365 but for google) There seems to be one app that is used and actually works very well. G Suite App Kyle Smith wrote it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Ephemeral Workspaces</title>
      <link>https://christopherja.rocks/posts/2020/01/aws-ephemeral-workspaces/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 13:05:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://christopherja.rocks/posts/2020/01/aws-ephemeral-workspaces/</guid>
      <description>AWS doesnt offer ephemeral workspaces at this point in time. So i was tasked with finding a solution and seeing if this was possible. Searching online i didnt find much. But i did find a way to work through this problem. Using lambda functions, Cloud Watch , Cloud Trail &amp;amp;Workspaces of course.
In my repo i have a pdf explaining how it works (hopefully well) its basically three lambda functions. One function triggers when a new workspace is created, and creates a cloud watch rule on it to see if it disconnects or logs off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BlackTabby C2 Server</title>
      <link>https://christopherja.rocks/posts/2020/01/blacktabby-c2-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 13:06:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://christopherja.rocks/posts/2020/01/blacktabby-c2-server/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to learn more about C2 Servers, so i tried to write my own. And i was semi-successful. It works. But its not neccesarily useful for others in my opinion. I think my biggest mistake was using couch db as the database. Using sqlLite would have been better i think. I will definitely pursue this again. As it wasnt as hard as i thought and most likely will try the same formula again but with a different DB and perhaps writing the server in C (As i think it would help me get better).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old Posts Found Here</title>
      <link>https://christopherja.rocks/posts/2020/01/old-posts-found-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 08:53:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://christopherja.rocks/posts/2020/01/old-posts-found-here/</guid>
      <description>Check out my OldSite that contains all my old posts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://christopherja.rocks/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://christopherja.rocks/about/</guid>
      <description>Christopher Alonso
 OSWE OSCE OSCP RHCE AZ-500 AZ-104 SEC+ CCNA  This is just a place for me to store my small notes on personal projects and findings while improving my skills. Hopefully some of my posts can be of use to others. Just as they have helped me.
Resume</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>